Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[♪ legendary music playing]
[♪ music ends]
[♪ exhilarating music playing]
All right. Kwana. you ready?
-[Kwana] I'm ready when you are.
-[Gramps] Huh?
Let's move out.
-[Gramps] They've spotted us!
-[Kara grunts]
-[gasps]
-They got here before us.
[Bhozn] Well. well.
you managed to survive.
Quite impressive.
However. we've kept
a nice little counterstrike waiting.
especially for you lot.
[droids whirring]
[Nawaam] All ships
assume attack formation.
Our target... the enemy fleet.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[hissing. clacking]
No! Stop! They're not warships.
They're carrying civilians!
[grunts] No!
Get us in front of the refugee fleet!
We'll serve as their shield.
[engines revving]
-[distant explosions]
-[all exclaiming]
-[rumbling]
-[whimpering]
[Kwana] Hurry!
[Juro] Curse you. Nawaam.
What a cheap and cowardly move.
You're attacking civilian ships
to try to smoke us out.
[Kwana] All ships form a protective shield
around the refugee convoy
and continue evacuation.
Get out of here.
Use your hyperdrives.
It doesn't matter where you go.
[♪ dramatic music continues playing]
[Bhozn] That big one
must be their flagship.
[Nawaam] All units. close in
on the enemy meteor ships.
We'll bring the fight to them.
[♪ sinister music playing]
[grunts]
[Four-Nines speaking Droid]
[sighs softly]
-[Four-Nines chirps]
-[gasps]
[footsteps approaching]
[Zhima] Can I help you?
I'm here to rescue you.
You're Lah Zhima. Is that right?
-[Four-Nines speaking Droid]
-[clanking]
[gasps. in English] Four-Nines!
And you are?
My name is Ethan. and I'm a friend.
I'm currently training under Master Juro.
I see.
Kara managed to get those lightsabers
to Juro after all.
[lasers firing]
[Nawaam] I sense something.
Could that be one of the Margrave's party?
[alarm beeping]
[Gramps] We're gonna crash!
Get ready to brace for impact!
-[grunting]
-[whimpers]
[crashing]
[all grunting]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Alert!
The enemy has breached the outer wall
and has entered level two. passage seven.
All hands. prepare for a firefight.
Don't let them get to the bridge.
I sense a presence.
What? Is it Sith?
[gasps] The one from Makoma Ko?
No.
Huh?
[grunting]
[gasps] What?
I'm sorry.
However. I'm afraid
that I am unable to leave this place.
At least not yet.
But now's our chance.
Nawaam has deployed most of his forces.
so there's hardly anyone aboard right now.
But that would mean
he's planning on taking out Bibin.
-Yes.
-[Zhima] So be it.
Ethan. you said it was?
You'll want to step aside.
Huh?
[rumbling]
[crashes]
[whooshes. thuds]
Come with me.
[both groan]
-[grunts]
-[clanks]
-[all groaning]
-[lasers firing]
Oh. no. The enemy
is now heading for the engine room.
They're attempting to attack us
where they think we're the weakest.
You're wrong.
I don't think that's it at all.
Think about what would happen if they
blew up the hyperdrive or fuel tank.
The entire ship would then be blown apart.
It seems that they've really
thought of everything.
Then we'll stop them. [grunts]
[sighs softly]
I need you to stay here. You're in charge.
Juro.
Homen. Kwana. we're going to
go out there and join the fray.
Are you ready?
Yes.
You bet.
-[grunts]
-[all exclaim]
[all groaning]
-[chuckles]
-[lasers firing]
[gasps]
[grunts]
Remain calm!
Our target is just up ahead. [grunts]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
-[grunts]
-[Kwana groans] Well. this is a letdown.
I was really hoping you'd have
put up more of a fight.
-[footsteps approaching]
-[grunts]
[lightsaber buzzing]
[grunts]
In any case. prepare yourselves.
[grunting]
So this is Nawaam's army.
Let's see what you're made of.
[gasps]
Hold on.
Someone's attacking from another route.
Inform the engine room.
No. wait!
The path they're taking
leads them straight here.
-The bridge.
-[gasps]
[♪ sinister music playing]
-[explosion]
-[crackling]
[lights popping. crackling]
-[grunts]
-[Gramps] Where are you going?
Well. I don't plan
on fighting him in here.
You're gonna go out there
and fight them by yourself?
Juro wanted me to protect the bridge.
so that's what I'm going to do.
Don't worry.
[crashes]
-[lights pop. crackle]
-[panting]
[grunts softly]
[♪ sinister music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
[popping. crackling]
-[footsteps approaching]
-[inhales]
[lightsaber buzzing]
-[lasers firing]
-[grunting]
[gasps] Nawaam!
[grunting] I'm sorry.
I must leave the rest to you.
-Go!
-Why? What happened?
[shudders] Wait are...you a...Jedi?
-[grunts]
-[Nawaam] Jedi?
Jedi... Sith...
These are archaic words
for someone so young.
The Jedi are everlasting.
[buzzes]
There's nothing archaic about them.
[Nawaam] I see.
You must be Lah Zhima's daughter then.
The one who caught old Gennoh off guard.
And what about you?
How do you know my father?
[Nawaam] Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Nawaam.
Lord Lah Zhima is the one I call master.
What are you saying?
My father would have
mentioned an apprentice.
[Nawaam] Would you like
to see for yourself?
[Kara] Don't be ridiculous.
I'm my father's only Padawan.
There have been no others.
I don't know why you're lying to me.
but you're going to give him back.
[Nawaam] Lord Zhima
will not return to you.
[grunting]
-[Nawaam] Hmm.
-[Kara yelling]
[lightsabers crackling]
[Kara grunting]
[gasps]
-[crackling]
-[grunts softly]
[gasps. grunts]
[whooshing. creaking]
[grunts. pants]
[panting]
[Nawaam] Impressive.
I should have expected no less
from my master's daughter.
Sticking to your lies?
When was it then?
When did my father take you on
as an apprentice?
Because this is the first
I've ever heard of it.
[Nawaam] I never said I learned
from his direct teachings.
He taught me an invaluable lesson
when I saw him cut down
his own master. Reno Tsutara.
It was then that I decided
to follow Lord Zhima as my master.
[whooshes]
[Nawaam] I remember... at that moment.
the urge to kill. the will to fight.
and even all traces of mercy
for Reno vanished.
All of his emotions disappeared.
leaving only an endless void
and nothingness.
[buzzes]
[explosion]
[lightsaber buzzes]
[Kara gasps. grunting]
[grunting]
-[grunts]
-[lightsabers crackling]
[Kara grunting]
[yelling]
Huh?
[clunking]
[shatters]
Hold on.
How old are you?
Did you actually see my father
strike down his own master?
[Nawaam] I did.
With my very own eyes.
[♪ somber music playing]
[lasers firing]
[Nawaam] That's when I vowed to walk
the path towards ultimate strength.
To achieve that state of nothingness.
The ideal state achieved by Lord Zhima.
What's so ideal about it?
[Nawaam] How sad.
I see you've been tainted
by Jedi teachings.
I shall show you what true power is.
A long time ago. I left a deep scar
on the heart of a young child.
warping his view of the world.
It ended up sending him on the wrong path.
And now it is my duty to counteract
the trauma the past has caused.
I'm not sure I know what you mean.
[whirring]
Enough stories.
Right now. we have to get
to Juro and Kara quickly.
And then find a way
to stop Nawaam's attack.
[both gasp]
[Gennoh] Well. if it isn't Lord Zhima.
Heading off somewhere?
[lightsabers whooshing. crackling]
[crashes]
[breathes heavily]
Your emotions have
too much control over you.
-[Kara gasps]
-[lightsabers crackling]
[Kara grunting]
-[Nawaam] That is why your blade wavers.
-[Kara yelps]
-[cracking]
-[gasps]
[gasping]
[grunts]
[groans]
[grunting]
[groaning]
-[hissing]
-[Kara whimpering]
[grunting]
[gasps]
-[distant crash]
-Huh?
-[crashes]
-[Kara gasps]
Juro!
This one is strong with the Force.
Kara. you have to get out of here.
[Kara] No! I'm going to make him tell me
where my father is!
Get out of here!
-[Nawaam] Margrave Juro.
-[Kara grunts]
I never imagined I would do battle
with a true Jedi.
[grunting]
And I never imagined
that the famed general would be so young.
Do you wear your mask
to conceal your youth?
-[Nawaam] What a boring question.
-[lightsabers crackling]
I use the mask to return to nothingness.
A cage to discipline my mind.
-"Return to nothingness"?
-Lord Lah Zhima attained nothingness.
I wish to achieve the state myself.
Enough with your lies!
My father isn't nothing.
Movements driven by rage
gives your enemy openings.
Shut up!
Kara! [grunts]
Your moves are skilled.
However. try as you might.
no Jedi can take me down.
[grunting]
-[gasps]
-[whooshes]
[Juro groans]
[winces. chokes]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[gasps]
[sighing] Juro...
Had you attained Lord Lah Zhima's
state of nothingness.
you would not have allowed
your Padawan to distract you.
[winces]
[screaming] Enough!
-[grunts]
-[Juro groans softly]
[crackling]
[breathes heavily]
[both yelping. groaning]
[weakly] Please run.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Juro! I won't leave you here.
Listen. Kara.
you are filled with kindness.
[breath trembling]
Do your best to always remember that.
If you do.
you will one day achieve true strength.
[gasps softly]
Here. This is yours.
[whimpers]
[sobbing]
[sobs. sniffles]
Juro...
[Kara sobs]
[screaming] Juro! [sobbing]
What was that?
What happened to my Master Juro?
Ethan. I will take care
of what I can here.
You need to get out of here
as fast as you can.
Escape and do your best to rescue
as many of your friends as possible.
Hold on a minute.
And. Ethan. please save my daughter. Kara.
[grunts softly]
Right.
Before I go. please take this.
[Gennoh] Are you done
saying your goodbyes?
Unlike yourself.
that brat isn't any sort of guest of ours.
And I'm not obligated to let him leave.
But as a courtesy to you. Lord Zhima.
I'll let him live if you beg.
Oh? And how will you stop him?
If you stop talking and let him go.
maybe I'll extend you the courtesy
of sparing your life.
[Gennoh] Quite a threat for a sabersmith.
Fire.
-[droids grunt]
-Go. Now!
[Ethan] Right.
-[lasers firing]
-[gasps] Four-Nines?
[whirring. crackling]
[thuds]
[speaking Droid]
[gasps]
[in English] I understand.
Protect Master Zhima.
[powering up]
[sighs]
[energy whooshing]
[Gennoh] What is happening to that blade?
[Four-Nines speaking Droid]
[in English] I swore to myself
I'd never draw you again.
[Gennoh] Interesting.
[whooshes]
[sobs. grunts]
It's like what happened before.
[Kara] Don't touch that.
[screaming] It isn't yours! [grunting]
-[energy trilling]
-[grunting]
[energy whooshes]
[buzzing]
[gasps] It turned silver.
The silver glow from the saber...
it's the same
as the light I saw that very day.
What are you saying?
[Nawaam] Don't you get it?
This is a lightsaber forged by Lord Zhima.
which reflects the user's heart.
Is that not right?
I still don't understand.
[Nawaam] The silver light means
I have already achieved the level
that Lord Zhima did on that fateful day.
This is beyond Jedi or Sith.
It's proof of a power
that can bring peace to the galaxy.
I won't allow you to conquer the galaxy.
Not with one of my father's blades.
All right.
Then see for yourself.
[grunts. gasps]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[straining]
[lightsabers crackling]
[grunting]
[whirring]
[lasers firing]
Retreat! Fall back!
[grunts] Hold on. Where are you going?
[grunts]
Hey. doesn't something seem off to you?
Hmm.
[gasps]
[explosion]
[Kara yelps]
[exclaims]
[screams]
-[rumbling]
-Damn it! All hands. evacuate!
[rumbling]
Move it! This place is going to blow!
Hey. where's Kara and Juro?
Have you seen them?
[Gramps] I assumed they were here already.
-[rumbling]
-[distant explosions]
Hold on. We're waiting for Kara and Juro.
[Gramps] It's gonna take more than this
to kill those two.
You guys are a different story.
And if I don't save your hide.
that girl will never forgive me.
Hmm. [grunts]
-[explosion]
-[powering up]
[Juro] Wake up. Kara. Open your eyes.
-[distant explosion]
-[grunts softly]
[groans]
[weakly] Juro...
[groans. sighs]
-[distant explosions]
-[whooshes]
[rumbling]
[groaning weakly]
-[explosion]
-[yelps]
[powering up]
-[explosions continue]
-[sighs]
[screams]
[groans]
[ships jumping to hyperspace]
Uh... Hmm.
[droid] All of their meteor ships
have been destroyed.
However. it appears a number
of their crew have escaped.
Do you want to go after them?
Leave them be.
Their forces have already been decimated
and their leader. Juro. is no more.
Dispatch the Hunters.
Have them dispose of the remaining Jedi.
What I must do now is conquer the galaxy.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[gasps]
[Ethan] Juro! Kara!
Homen!
Anyone. please come in!
[whooshes]
[♪ dramatic music continues playing]
[♪ music concludes]
[♪ theme music playing]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org